

VINOTH KUMAR

PROFILE

I have five plus years experiences on graphics designing and one who has a strong passion and interest for design. To acquire a position that affords me the opportunity to bring my technical expertise. problem solving skills and welling ness to learn to make an organisation successful, I firmly believe in the principle of implementing my duties with dedication and determination.

CONTACT



No. 188 Drowpathy Amman Koil Street Annamedu Village Thiruninravur Tiruvallur, 602024



+91 9884227193



vino.a619@gmail.com

PERSONAL SKILLS

- 1. Maintain a Positive & professional attitude
- 2. Interior decors
- 3. Digital Skills
- 4. Honesty & Confidence
- 5. Good Communication
- 6. Multi-tasking

EDUCATION

GRT IET Tirutani / Anna University's

Bachelor of Engineering- EEE(2014) 65.49 %

JAYA Matic Hr.Sec.School

Secondary school 2010 62.58%

SRI RAMAKRISHNA Matric Hr.Sec.School

Matriculation 2008 63.40%

LANGUANGES

English		0	•	•	•
Tamil		•	•	•	•
Telgu		•	•	•	•
Malay	•	•	•	•	•

SKILLS

Adobe XD

Illustrator	•	•	•	•	•
Photoshop	•		•	•	•
Premiere Pro			•	•	•
FIGMA	•	•	•	•	•
Affter Effects	•		•	•	•
Corel Draw					_
Google Web	•	•	•		•
Designer		•	•	•	•

EXPERIENCES

CTI SIGNAGES SDN BHD - 2015-2020

Graphic Designer for digital marketing for QSR Brands (m) holdings bhd Pizza Hut . KFC and A&I. RHB and Hong long banks .Movie industrys. promotion for events etc.

BUY HAPPY MARKETING LLP - 2021 - 2022

Graphic Designer for social media marketing for VIP hair colour shampoo, VIP snore care oil & 18 herbs organic poducts.

THE INDUS VALLEY - 2022 - PRESENT

Graphic Designer for social media & google ads for kitchenware products

JOB RESPONSIBILITY

- Prepares work to be accomplished by gathering informat onand materials
- plans concepts by studying informat on and materials.
- illustrates concept bydesigning rough layout of art and copy regarding arrangementsize.type size and style and related concepts
- obta ins approvalof concept by submitting roughlayoutfor approval.
- prepares finished copy and art by operating typesetting.printing and similar equipment and purchasing from vendors.
- prepares finallayout by marking and pastingup finished copy and art.
- ensures operation of equipment by completing preventivemaintenance requirements.following manufacturers instruct ions. troubleshooting malfunction calling for repairs and evaluating new equipment.
- completes projec t s by coordinating with outside agencies.art services. printing etc
- maintains technical Knowledge by attending design workshop and participating in professional societies.
- contributes to team effort by accomplishing related results as needed.

https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/llqmsmDHEk5P5PZIt5FT×SH_b3-009Zd7?usp=sharing